A seasoned digital marketing professional with global experience

PROFILE

I am a seasoned digital marketing professional with extensive global experience in building, maintaining, and running successful digital, and traditional marketing campaigns.

Over the past 20+ years, I have implemented numerous large scale projects, including, websites, mobile & desktop applications, email campaigns, corporate branding, and omni-channel marketing initiatives.

I bring a rare amount of knowledge in visual design, user experience, typography, color theory, and creative problem solving skills to any business and/or clients I work with.

I have worked in various highly regulated industries, including; advertising, education, medical, insurance, finance, and mortgage origination.

I have extensive experience in usability, design iteration, A/B & multivariate testing to measure, and improve the performance of various web applications. I use artificial intelligence to help with research and ideation.

I'm able to take a vague concept on a napkin or formal requirements to a successful marketing strategy or product experience.

Experienced with Adobe Creative Suite (Photoshop, Illustrator, InDesign, DreamWeaver, Premiere Pro & After Effects), Jira, Figma, Adobe XD, Sketch, InVision, Zeplin, Salesforce, SFMC, and most other mainstream CMS/CRM tools.

Building strong, trusting relationships with peers and executives is vital to my approach. I have a proven track record in leading remote, off-shore, and in-office teams. Committed to lifelong learning; I continuously update my skills and sharing my accumulated wisdom whenever possible.

Besides mentoring my professional peers, I have also mentored minority high school students in graphic design, typography, photography, and internet skills.



SKILLS

- Design, Passion, and Curiousity.
- Multi-Channel Marketing
 Campaign Management.
- Usability, Design Iteration, A/B, and Multivariate Testing.
- CMS, CRM, Digital, Content, and Email Marketing.
- Advanced Marketing Analytics &
 KPI Reporting Skills.
- Effective communication, and collaboration abilities.
- Exceptional attention to detail.

CONTACT

A seasoned digital marketing professional with global experience

EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF ARTS - GRAPHIC DESIGNMedia College - Amsterdam, The Netherlands
September - 1995

FUNDAMENTAL & ADVANCED HTML CODINGMedia College - Amsterdam, The Netherlands
August - 1996

WORK EXPERIENCE

PENNYMAC - Manager, Web OptimizationMarch 2019 - Present

- Developed & executed multi-channel digital media strategies, and roadmaps aligned with company growth and success goals.
- Closely tracked the latest digital marketing technologies, trends, and strategies to identify opportunities to enhance, and improve the business digital marketing roadmaps.
- Continuously evaluated company consumer-facing web properties, and executing on measurable optimization efforts by leading a highly effective testing team. Expert leader in ideating market relevant hypotheses, and, deep diving into analytics data to increase user engagement, in order to provide a steady stream of high converting leads for company sales teams.
- Juggled multiple high-visibility projects, and ensured quality & timely content delivery for multiple LOB's across the organization.
- Comfortable, and highly proficient in launching new, and maintaining existing consumer & B2B facing web solutions in a highly regulated business environment.
- Excellent working knowledge of most mainstream digital marketing tools such as: SFMC, HTML, CSS, jQuery, Chrome DevTools, Jekyll, Liquid, Yaml, etc. CMS: CloudCannon, LifeRay, WordPress, etc. G-Suite, MS Office Suite, Tableau, SnowFlake, Leadspedia, Rundeck, Jenkins, GitHub & AWS. Figma, Abobe Creative & Experience Suites, Screaming Frog, VWO, UserTesting, Optimizely, Target, HotJar, SEMrush, GA4, Tag Manager 360, etc.



SKILLS

- Design, Passion, and Curiousity.
- Multi-Channel Marketing
 Campaign Management.
- Usability, Design Iteration, A/B, and Multivariate Testing.
- CMS, CRM, Digital, Content, and Email Marketing.
- Advanced Marketing Analytics &
 KPI Reporting Skills.
- Effective communication, and collaboration abilities.
- Exceptional attention to detail.

CONTACT

A seasoned digital marketing professional with global experience

WORK EXPERIENCE

AGIA AFFINITY - Manager, Digital Marketing 2014 - 2019

- Spearheaded client meetings to determine project needs and professional requirements and identify the correct course of action to help clients be successful.
- Maintained expert-level skills in digital platforms such as SalesForce Marketing Cloud, Adobe Creative Suite, Liferay CMS, Google Analytics, and Tableau.
- Drove digital and enterprise collaboration across functional teams, focusing on delivery and continuous process improvement.
- Devised strategies and roadmaps to support product vision and value to the business.
- Administered marketing calendar and posted new content to coincide with new product, and service releases.

DAVID ALLEN COMPANY - Multimedia Designer 2012 - 2014

- Executed designs that adhered to the overall creative vision and direction.
- Oversaw all phases of video production for coaching talent promotional pieces, from preto post-production.
- Developed collateral such as display, marketing, and packaging materials to support product branding strategies.
- Employed brand design fundamentals when selecting typography, composition, layout, and color in design work.

STERLING HEALTHCARE INFO SYSTEMS - Art Director 2008 - 2012

- Developed artistic visual products while working within defined technical guidelines.
- Maintained accurate specs by adhering to print and art specification standards.
- Approved art layouts, copy design, and illustrative work for publication.
- Designed new on-brand visual elements to effectively convey concepts and messaging.
- Juggled multiple projects and tasks to ensure high-quality and timely delivery.



SKILLS

- Design, Passion, and Curiousity.
- Multi-Channel Marketing
 Campaign Management.
- Usability, Design Iteration, A/B, and Multivariate Testing.
- CMS, CRM, Digital, Content, and Email Marketing.
- Advanced Marketing Analytics &
 KPI Reporting Skills.
- Effective communication, and collaboration abilities.
- Exceptional attention to detail.

CONTACT

A seasoned digital marketing professional with global experience

WORK EXPERIENCE

ADDITIONAL MARKETING EXPERIENCE 1996 - 2009

- Various Graphic & Motion Design roles (USA & International)
- I will happily provide additional details regarding my previous work experiences beyond this timeframe, upon request.

ACCOMPLISHMENTS

- Pennymac MAP Manager Accelerator Program, Thousand Oaks, CA.
- Pennymac PM Silver Certification, Thousand Oaks, CA.
- Google GTM Certified by LunaMetrics, Pittsburgh, PA.
- Google Adwords Certified by LunaMetrics, Franklin, TN.
- Tableau Desktop I: Fundamentals Certified by Tableau, Wexford, PA.
- · Liferay Symposium NA 2015, Chicago, IL.
- GPS Leadership Training Certified by AGIA, Carpinteria, CA.
- HIPPA Compliance Training Certified by AGIA, Carpinteria, CA.
- GTD® Fundamentals Workflow Coaching Certified by David Allen Company, Ojai, CA.

WEBSITES

- https://pennymac.com/
- https://corr.pennymac.com/
- https://tpo.pennymac.com/
- https://agia.com/
- https://gettingthingsdone.com/
- https://www.sterlinghcs.com/

LANGUAGES

- English
- Dutch



SKILLS

- Design, Passion, and Curiousity.
- Multi-Channel Marketing
 Campaign Management.
- Usability, Design Iteration, A/B, and Multivariate Testing.
- CMS, CRM, Digital, Content, and Email Marketing.
- Advanced Marketing Analytics &
 KPI Reporting Skills.
- Effective communication, and collaboration abilities.
- Exceptional attention to detail.

CONTACT